---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&difficulty=easy
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:19:29 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=3bee96c17e9fed37d58a755cd6326051; path=/
      Upgrade:
      - h2
      Connection:
      - Upgrade
      Vary:
      - User-Agent
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who
        played Deputy Marshal Samuel Gerard in the 1993 film &quot;The Fugitive&quot;?","correct_answer":"Tommy
        Lee Jones","incorrect_answers":["Harrison Ford","Harvey Keitel","Martin Landau"]},{"category":"Science:
        Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Linus Torvalds
        created Linux and Git.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which
        of the following African countries was most successful in resisting colonization?","correct_answer":"Ethiopia","incorrect_answers":["C&ocirc;te
        d&rsquo;Ivoire","Congo","Namibia"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In
        which year did the Invasion of Kuwait by Iraq occur?","correct_answer":"1990","incorrect_answers":["1992","1988","1986"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"You can legally
        drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The main playable
        character of the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot; is a monster.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Mythology","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which
        Greek &amp; Roman god was known as the god of music, truth and prophecy, healing,
        the sun and light, plague, poetry, and more?","correct_answer":"Apollo","incorrect_answers":["Aphrodite","Artemis","Athena"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which Final
        Fantasy game consisted of a female-only cast of party members?","correct_answer":"Final
        Fantasy X-2","incorrect_answers":["Final Fantasy IX","Final Fantasy V","Final
        Fantasy XIII-2"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        war is Call Of Duty: Black Ops based on?","correct_answer":"Cold War","incorrect_answers":["WW3","Vietnam","WW1"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the video
        game &quot;Postal 2&quot;, what is the name of Postal Dude&#039;s dog?","correct_answer":"Champ","incorrect_answers":["Snoopy","Krotchy","Duke"]}]}'
  recorded_at: Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:19:29 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
